agkidzone.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy Policy - CloudCo

**CloudcoEntertainment.com Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date:  This policy was updated and became effective on 1/30/19**

CloudocoEntertainment.com is a website featuring games, videos, and online and downloadable activities for kids. We recognize that visitors to our Site will include children younger than the age of 13 (Children).  As required by The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we provide this privacy policy to inform parents and legal guardians (collectively, Parents) about our privacy practices.

This Privacy Statement explains our privacy practices for CloudocoEntertainment.com and any other website or other interactive features, applications, or downloads that are operated by Cloudco Entertainment (hereinafter “Cloudco”) and hosted by Cloudco and that link to this Privacy Policy (the Site), whether accessed via computer, mobile device or otherwise. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Site and does not cover information collected offline by Cloudco (unless specifically stated) nor does it apply to our other websites or mobile apps that do not link to this Privacy Policy.

Please review our full privacy policy below – but here are some key points to know:

The Site does not require Children or any visitor to provide their name, address, or other contact information in order to play the games or access other content on the Site. 

In order to keep the Site free, we have advertisements on the Site. We work with ad companies to facilitate the placement of these advertisements. However, we use only contextual-advertising methods and not interest-based (a/k/a behavioral) advertising methods.

The Site, and its third-party service and content providers, may gather IP address, usage data and other information for analytical and other internal-operations purposes by means of cookies, beacons, and other technologies. 

Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review our [Terms of Use](http://www.agkidzone.com/terms-of-use), which govern your use of the Site.

**This Privacy Policy explains:**

  1.    [INFORMATION THE SITE COLLECTS](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#info)
  2.    [DISCLOSURE OF CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION TO SERVICE PROVIDERS](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#disclose)
  3.    [THIRD-PARTY ANALYTICS PROVIDERS AND AD SERVERS](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#third)
  4.    [LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#links)
  5.    ONLINE TRACKING
  6.    [PARENT’S RIGHTS](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#parents)
  7.    [CHANGES TO OUR POLICY](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#changes)
  8.    [CONTACT US](http://www.agkidzone.com/privacy-policy#contact)

**INFORMATION THE SITE COLLECTS**

_Information Collected_. This section describes the Personal Information and Other Information the Site collects from visitors.

_Personal Information._ Personal Information is information that could reasonably be used to contact you or to identify you personally ( _for example_ , first and last name, mailing address or telephone number). Personal Information also includes your IP address or other unique identifier that is associated, on a persistent or on-going basis, with your computer, mobile phone or other device you use to access the Site (Device Identifier). The Site does not generally collect name, address, or other contact information from visitors who play games or participate in other activities on the Site. However, we and our third-party service providers may collect your Device Identifier when you visit the Site. We, and our third party service providers, use this information solely to support the Site’s internal operations, including maintaining, securing, and analyzing the functioning of the Site and serving contextual advertisements.

The Site may also, on limited occasions, collect first name and online contact information (typically, an e-mail address) from Children solely for the following purposes:

For one-time use of that information, such as to respond directly to a specific request (for example, answering a question submitted through the Site). We delete the contact information provided from our records once it is used to fulfill the specific one-time purpose and will not use it to re-contact the Child.

For the sole purpose of any of the following: to protect the security or integrity of the Site; to take precautions against liability; to respond to judicial process; and, to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety.

If the Site offers a feature that collects Personal Information in addition to the information described above, we will, where required by COPPA, provide the Child’s Parent prior notice of the Site’s privacy practices and obtain the Parent’s consent before collecting the Child’s Personal Information. If you believe your Child is participating in an activity that collects Personal Information and you or another Parent have not received an email providing notice or seeking your consent, please contact us. We will not use Parent emails provided for parental consent purposes to market to the Parent, unless the Parent has expressly opted in to email marketing or has separately participated in an activity that allows for such email contact.

Please note that, as required by law, we will not condition a Child’s participation in an activity on the Site on the Child’s disclosing more than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity. We use Personal Information only for the purpose that it was provided and for internal purposes, except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Public Disclosure**

The Site does not enable Children to make Personal Information publicly available.

**Ongoing Communications**

We may collect a Child’s email address in order to communicate with that Child more than once, such as for providing a newsletter. For such purposes, we will retain the Child’s email address solely for such communication purposes and for no other reason. Whenever we collect a Child’s online contact information for ongoing communications, we will simultaneously require a Parent email address in order to notify the Parent about the collection and use of the Child’s information, as well as to provide the Parent an opportunity to prevent further contact with the Child.

**Parental Consent**

In the event we wish to collect Personal Information from a Child, COPPA requires that we first seek a Parent’s consent by email. In the email we will explain what information we are collecting, how we plan to use it, how the Parent can provide consent, and how the Parent can revoke consent. If we receive confirmation via email from the Parent, we will take an additional step to confirm the Parent’s consent, which may be to contact the Parent again via email or by phone, fax, or mail. A Parent may consent to Cloudco collecting certain Personal Information about a Child, but not consent to disclosing that Personal Information to a third party. If we do not receive parental consent within a reasonable time, we will delete the Parent contact information and any other information collected from the Child in connection with that activity.

**Other Information**

In addition, we and our third-party service providers (including any third-party content providers) may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Site (Usage Information). Usage Information may include the browser and operating system you are using, the URL or advertisement that referred you to our Site, the search terms you entered into a search engine that lead you to our Site (if applicable), all of the areas within our Site that you visit, and the time of day, among other information. We may use Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including enhancing or otherwise improving the Site and our products and services. Usage Information is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we treat it as Personal Information.  

_Technologies Used to Collect Information_. The technologies that may be used by us and our third-party service providers to collect Personal and Usage Information include the following:

_Cookies_. We use a technology called cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your device for a variety of purposes. Cookies may be used for many purposes, such as supporting game play and other activities available on the Site, as well as for analytics and similar internal purposes. A Flash cookie is a data file placed on a device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built into or downloaded by you to your device. Flash cookies may be used for various purposes, including, without limitation, enabling a Flash feature and remembering your preferences. For more information about Flash and the privacy choices Adobe offers, visit: [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser settings to notify you when you’ve received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on the Site if you choose not to accept or delete cookies or to adjust your Flash privacy settings.

_Web Beacons_. When you visit the Site, we or our third-party service providers (such as advertising companies, advertisers and analytics companies) may set web beacons (small graphic images or other web programming code, also known as 1x1 GIFs or clear GIFs) and similar technologies on our Site. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on your computer such as cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Site, to monitor how users navigate the Site, and to improve your experience on the Site.

_Embedded Scripts_. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

_Third-party Operators_. The list of third-party operators who collect persistent identifiers on the Site may be found here. Please contact us with questions about the privacy policies of any such third-party operators..

**DISCLOSURE OF CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION TO SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We do not disclose Children’s Personal Information to third parties, except with regard to the safety and security of the Site as discussed above or as described in this paragraph. We may also disclose Children’s Personal Information to service providers who provide support for the internal operations of the Site and who do not disclose or use the Personal Information for any other purpose. These service providers may provide support services such as hosting the Site or content available on the Site, designing and/or operating the Site’s features, or performing other administrative services. We may provide these companies with access to Children’s Personal Information in order for them to carry out the services they are performing on our behalf.

**THIRD-PARTY ANALYTICS PROVIDERS AND AD SERVERS**

We work with network advertisers, ad agencies, third-party traffic-measurement services, and other service providers to serve advertisements on the Site and to provide us with information regarding traffic on the Site, including the pages viewed and the actions users take when visiting the Site. Our service providers may set and access their own tracking technologies on your device (including cookies and web beacons) and may collect or have access to your Personal Information and other information about you (such as Usage Information), provided that any Personal Information collected will be limited to your Device Identifier and will be used only to support the internal operations of the Site. We may share Usage Information about visitors with third-party advertising companies, analytics providers and other vendors for similar purposes.  

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

The Site may contain links to third-party web sites that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy or data collection practices of any third party.

**ONLINE TRACKING**

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not have your online activities tracked. Although the Site does not recognize “do not track” features, we do not engage in any online behavioral advertising with Personal Information collected from the Site.

**PARENT’S RIGHTS**

Parents have the right to review and request that Cloudco delete any Personal Information that the Site has collected and retained about their Child and to refuse to permit Cloudco to collect any further Personal Information from a Child. If you would like to request that Cloudco delete any Personal Information we may have about your Child (such as first name and contact information for use in sending our newsletter) or if you would like to request that the Site make no further collection of Personal Information from your Child, please contact us as described in the [Contact Us](http://www.agkidzone.com/contact-us)section.

**CHANGES TO OUR POLICY**

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time and any changes will be effective upon posting. If we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will update the Effective Date above and we will display a notice on the Site. However, we will obtain Parental consent prior to using or disclosing Personal Information of a Child in a manner materially different from the Privacy Policy posted at the time of collection and any prior Parental consent received.

This Privacy Statement explains our privacy practices for CloudocoEntertainmen.com and any other website or other interactive features, applications, or downloads that are operated by Cloudco Entertainment (hereinafter “Cloudco”) and hosted by Azure and that link to this Privacy Policy (the Site), whether accessed via computer, mobile device or otherwise. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Site and does not cover information collected offline by Cloudco (unless specifically stated) nor does it apply to our other websites or mobile apps that do not link to this Privacy Policy.

**CONTACT US**

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy and use of Children’s Personal Information should be directed to Cloudco by any of the following methods:

_Cloudco Entertainment_

1468 West 9thStreet, Suite 100

Cleveland, Ohio 44113-1252
